RG 030, Council of Defense
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. General
  - 1. Classified file, 1917-1919
    - E. Publicity (Box 17)
      - E20: Bulletins Boards - Replies to Town Questionnaire (Box 19)
      - E21: “Why Germany Wants Peace Now” (The Prussian Blot) - Requests and Remarks re Poster (Box 19)
      - E21: “Courage Comrades, I'm Coming” - Poster (Box 19)
      - E21: Liberty Loan Poster - Correspondence, 1918 April 10 (Box 19)
      - E21: Replies to Poster “Will You Display War Posters?” (Box 19)
      - E21: Correspondence with Posting Agents re Care of Bulletin Boards (Box 19)
      - E21: Posters (Material about) (Box 19)
      - E21.1: List of stations where Bulletins can be posted N.Y., N.H., & H. R.R. (Box 19)
      - E21.2: News Photos Posters (Box 19)
      - E21.2: F.D. Roosevelt - Message to the Men and Women of Connecticut (Box 19)
      - E21.2: News Photo Posters [Requests for] (Box 20)
      - E21.4: Requests for Posters or Publications - Business Concerns (Box 20)
      - E21.4a: Requests for posters or Publications (Box 20)
      - E22: Newspapers (Box 20)
      - E22: “Made in Connecticut” War Interviews (Box 20)
      - E22.1: “Made in Connecticut” War Interviews with Women (Box 20)
      - E23: News bulletins (Box 20)
      - E24: Press Notices (Very General) (Box 20)
      - E24: “Bidwell Story” (Box 20)
      - E25: Newspaper Representatives (Box 20)
      - E25: Special Representatives on Newspapers (Box 20)
      - E26: Transportation for Newspapers (Box 21)
      - E27: Foreign Language Newspapers (Box 21)
      - E28: [Division of Press Cooperation] (Box 21)
      - E30: Permission to Print Legal Papers to be Kept (Box 21)
      - E30: [List of Liberty Choruses] (in Black Binder) (Box 21)
      - E30: Liberty Chorus Division, Council of Defense, Organizing Forms, 1918 (Box 21)
      - E30: Liberty Choruses (Box 21)
      - E30: Council of Defense, Div. of Liberty Choruses - Bulletins of Department, 1918 (Box 21)
      - E31: Patriotic Songs (Box 21)
      - E31.1: Songs Composed by Various People (Box 21)
      - E34: Rallies (Box 21)
      - E34: War Rallies Division - Record book (Black Book) (Box 21)
      - E34c: [War Savings Series - Permits and Confirmation of Rallies] (Box 22)
      - E34c: [War Rally Series - Permits and Confirmation of Rallies] (Box 22)
      - E34c: Confirmations of Arrangements for War Rallies (Box 22)
      - E34.02: Orders for Posters & Handbills, Division of War Rallies, War Savings (Box 22)
      - E34.02: Orders for Posters and Handbills, Division of War Rallies (Box 23)
      - E34.02: Orders for Posters and Handbills, Division War Rallies, Section (Box 23)
      - E34.03: Italian War Rally, 1918 March 10 (Box 23)
      - E34.04: [Eastford War Rally], 1918 April 3 (Box 23)
      - E34.05: [Information for the Press re War Rallies] (Box 23)
      - E34.07: [Scottish War Rally], 1918 June 4 (Box 23)
      - E34.08: Jewish War Rally, 1918 June 2 (Box 23)
      - E34.09: Pershing’s Veterans for [Speaking Tours] (Box 23)
      - E34.09: Data re Meeting Addressed by Perishing Veterans (Box 23)
      - E34.09: Pershing Men [Poster] (Box 23)
      - E34.10: Meeting at Parson’s, Addressed by Dr. Scherer and Paul Perigord (Box 23)
      - E34.11: French Army Band, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - E34.12: Lafayette-Marne Day Observance (Box 23)
      - E35: Rally Week (Box 23)
      - E36: Roosevelt War Rally (Box 23)
      - E37: Halls (Box 23)
      - E38: Speakers - Suspense (Mr. Dunham) (Box 24)
      - E38: Rally Week Speakers (Mr. Dunham) (Box 24)
      - E38: Speakers and Speaking Material (Box 24)
      - E38.011: Speakers (Mr. Dunham) (Box 24)
      - E38.011: Lists of Speakers (Box 24)
      - E38.09: Confidential Reports on Speaking and Rallies (Box 24)
      - E38.09: Confidential Speaker Lists (Box 24)
      - E38.4: Military Speakers (Box 24)
      - ------: [List of Speakers] (Black Binder) (Box 25)
      - ------: [List of Four Minute Men] (Black Binder) (Box 25)
      - E38.5: Four Minute Men (Box 25)
      - E38.506: Meeting of Four Minute Men, 1917 October 8 (Box 25)
      - E38.51: Committee on Public Information - Div. of Four Minute Men - Army Bulletins (Box 25)
      - E39: [Western Tour of George B. Chandler] (Box 25)
      - E40: Celebration for Drafted Men (Box 25)
      - E50: Memorials (Box 25)
      - E50.1: Memorials, List of those Sent out (Box 25)
      - E50.2: Memorials - Correspondence with War Bureaus and Local People (A-Z), 2 folders (Box 26)
      - E50.3: Memorials - Correspondence with People Outside of Connecticut (Memorials of other States) (Box 26)
      - E50.4: Casualty Lists - Letters re (Box 26)
      - E51: Condolences (Box 26)
      - E60: Christmas Buying (Box 26)
      - E63: Solf Propaganda (Box 26)
      - E75: Moving Pictures (Box 26)
      - E75.1: Correspondence re Using Guy Hedlund as Moving Picture Director (Box 26)
      - E100: Correspondence re Pay Envelopes (Box 26)
    - F. Legal (Box 27)
      - F25: Soldier’s and Sailor’s Civil Relief Act (Box 27)
      - F25: Soldier’s and Sailor’s Civil Rights Bill (Box 27)
      - F30: [Press Release - Resource Mobilization Bureau] (Box 27)
      - F31: Letter Stating That Home Service Section of Red Cross Should Arrange for Establishment of Legal Committees, 1918 April 6 (Box 27)
      - F31: Legal Committees of War Bureaus (Box 27)
      - F32: Bureau of Soldier’s and Sailor’s Information (Box 27)
      - F50: Legal Information for Soldiers and Sailors (Box 27)
      - F75: Proposed War Legislation (Box 27)
    - G. Coordination of Societies (Box 27)
      - -----: [Lists of Societies] Lists of Connecticut Societies and Organizations (Box 27)
      - -----: [Lists of Societies, Associations (Including Hartford)] - (Black Binder) Letter to Lodges and Clubs of Connecticut, 1917 October 19 (Box 27)
      - G02: Mr. William’s Correspondence (Box 28)
      - G05: Replies to Pamphlet “How to Serve Without Waste of Time or Energy” (Box 28)
      - G05: Re Pamphlet Sent Out by Council Entitled “How to Serve without Waste of Time or Energy” (Box 28)
      - -----: [Soldier’s Big brother Movement] (Box 28)
      - G16: Red Cross (Box 28)
      - -----: [Lists of Men’s Societies] (Black Binder) (Box 28)
      - G16: Red Cross Branches and Chapters - Lists (Box 29)
      - -----: Red Cross Calendar (Box 29)
      - G16: Red Cross Message (Box 29)
      - G16: Letter To Red Cross Chapters, re Cooperation Between the Civilian Relief Committees and other Charitable Agencies, 1917 September 26 (Box 29)
      - G16.03: Red Cross Bulletin and News Letter (Box 29)
      - G16.08: Red Cross Circular Letters (Box 29)
      - G16.1: Junior Red Cross (Box 29)
      - G16.2: Red Cross Campaign, 1918 May (Box 29)
      - G16.21: Advertising for Red Cross Drive, 1918 May (Box 29)
      - G16.22: Posters - Red Cross Campaign, 1918 May (Box 29)
      - G16.5: Italian Red Cross (Box 30)
      - G69: National League for Women’s Service (Box 30)
      - G150: Relief and Welfare Charities (Box 30)
      - G201: [Meeting - Conn. Commandery, Military Order of Foreign Wars] (Box 30)
      - G401: Knights of Columbus (Box 30)
      - G500: New Enterprises In General. Warning Against Entering Upon Without First Consulting Council (Box 30)
      - G501: Individual Funds Approved or Investigated by Council (Letters in Regard to) (Box 30)
      - G501.1: Smileage Book Correspondence (Arranged by Town Alphabetically) A-M. (Box 30)
      - G501.1: Smileage Book Correspondence with towns, N-Z (Box 31)
      - G501.1: Smileage Book Correspondence with Military Entertainment Council (Box 31)
      - G501.1: Smileage Books - Circular Letters, posters, etc. Advertising Matters, Mailing List (Box 32)
      - G501.1: Smileage Correspondence with Messrs Wayne and Broadhead (Box 32)
      - G501.1: Press Notices re Smileage Books, Military Entertainment Council, etc. (Also Requisitions and Registry) (Box 32)
      - G501.1: Smileage Reports (Box 32)
      - G501.2: Boy Scouts (Box 32)
      - G501.3: Navy Relief Society (Box 32)
      - G501.4: Blue Cross, Red Star (Box 32)
      - G501.5: Clark C. Griffith Ball and Bat Fund (Box 32)
      - G501.6: Fund for Starving Belgian Children (Box 32)
      - G501.7: North American Civic League For Immigrants (Box 32)
      - G501.8: League for National Unity (Box 32)
      - G501.9: Bohemian National League (Box 32)
      - G501.10: Women’s National League, Washington, DC (Box 32)
      - G501.11: Belgian Artist Committee & other Belgian Societies (Box 32)
      - G501.12: Democracy Emblem Committee (Box 32)
      - G501.13: American Hungarian Loyalty League (Box 32)
      - G501.14: Conference Committee on National Preparedness (Box 32)
      - G501.15: American Alliance and Institute of Freedom, Plan By J.A. Solandt (Box 32)
      - G501.16: American Chocolate Funds (Box 33)
      - G501.17: Treasure & Trinket Fund (Box 33)
      - G501.18: American & Syrian Relief (Box 33)
      - G501.19: [Union League Club] (Box 33)
      - G501.20: [The American Committee for a Devastated France] (Box 33)
      - G501.21: United Committee on War Temperance (Box 33)
      - G501.22: Souvenir Rosters (Box 33)
      - G501.23: [Connecticut Children’s Aid Society] (Box 33)
      - G501.24: [British and Canadian Patriotic Fund] (Box 33)
      - G501.25: America’s Allies Cooperative Committee (Box 33)
      - G501.26: Lutheran Brotherhood (Box 33)
      - G501.27: American Flag House and Betsy Ross Memorial (Box 33)
      - G501.28: American Defense Society (Box 33)
      - G501.29: Junior American Guard (Box 33)
      - G501.30: Over Seas Club London (Box 33)
      - G501.31: Stars and Stripes Club, Manchester, England (Box 33)
      - G501.32: 76th Division Tobacco Fund (Box 33)
      - G501.33: [Connecticut Patriotic League] (Box 33)
      - G501.34: American Friends of Musicians in France (Box 33)
      - G501.35: New England Home for Little Wanderers (Box 33)
      - G501.36: Sherman Service (Box 33)
      - G501.37: American Flag Society, American Honor Roll (Box 33)
      - G501.38: [Unconditional Surrender Clubs] (Box 33)
      - G501.39: [Harry Lauder Five Million Dollar Fund] (Box 33)
      - G501.40: [Fatherless Children of France] (Box 33)
      - G501.41: Polish National Department - Polish victims Relief Fund (Box 33)
      - G501.42: Italian War Relief Fund of America (Box 33)
      - G501.43: Oriental Esoteric Library League (Box 33)
      - G501.44: [National Civic Federation Review] (Box 34)
      - G501.45: Perishing Fourth of July Fund, Raised by United Spanish War Veterans (Box 34)
      - G501.46: Woman’s National Honor Medal (Box 34)
      - G501.47: Harlem League of Clubs (Box 34)
      - G501.48: Mothers of Defenders of Democracy (Box 34)
      - G501.49: Women’s Oversea Hospitals (Box 34)
      - G503: Other Outside Funds (Box 34)
      - G504: Lists of Approved Organizations, and lists Showing (Box 34)
      - G504: Requests for our List of Approved Funds (Box 34)
      - G505: Chain Letters. (Box 34)
      - G70: Mother’s and Parent Teacher’s Associations (Box 34)
      - G85: YWCA (Box 34)
      - G90: YMCA (Box 34)
      - G91: YMCA War Work Fund, Replies by County Committees (Box 34)
      - G91: YMCA War Work Fund, Replies By Town Chairmen (Box 34)
      - G91: YMCA War Work Fund, Replies to Letter of Oct. 30 (Box 34)
      - G902: [Voluntary Associations and Societies] (Box 34)
      - G937.05: [Oregon and Ohio State Councils of Defense Newsletters] (Box 34)
      - G938: [Statement of Organization and Function of Department of Allied Bodies, Committee of Public Safety, Pennsylvania] (Box 34)
    - H. Food Supply (Box 35)
      - H: Food Supply and Conservation (Box 35)
      - H01: Local Food Administrators (Box 35)
      - H01: [Letter from Gov. Holcomb] (Box 35)
      - H01: Circular by Mr. Also [re Appointment of local Food Administrators] (Box 35)
      - H01: List of Local Food Committees “Original Lists” (Envelope) (Box 35)
      - H03: [Federal Food Administration, Washington, D.C.] (Box 35)
      - H04: [Council of National Defense - “What the States are Doing”] (Box 35)
      - H05: Bulletins - Connecticut State Council of Defense, Committee of Food Supply (Envelope) (Box 35)
      - H05: [Bulletins re Potatoes] (Box 35)
      - H06: Meetings of Food Supply Committee (Box 35)
      - H11: [Problem of the Unemployed and the American Farmer - Speeches by Hon. Warren Worth Bailey.] (Box 35)
      - H12: [Suggested Topics For Campaign For increased Planting] (Box 35)
      - H18: [Letter From Boston re Slaughter of Cattle] (Box 35)
      - H20.05: Press Bulletins - Publicity Bureau (Box 35)
      - H24: Food Posters (Box 35)
      - H25: Fairs and Exhibits - General Material - Press Data, Reports, Circular Letters and Misc. (Box 35)
      - H25: Connecticut State Council of Defense - War Exhibits (Photo’s in Black Book) (Box 36)
      - H25.01: Fairs and Exhibits - General Correspondence (Box 36)
      - H25.01: Knights of Columbus - Correspondence re their Exhibits at Fairs (Box 36)
      - H25.01: Red Cross Correspondence, Including that with Mabel Wilcox re missing box of exhibits (Box 36)
      - H25.01: Warren, Alfred and Flaherty, Daniel- Correspondence (Box 36)
      - H25.01: Correspondence re Washington Matters (Box 36)
      - H25.01: Correspondence re Transportation For Fairs- Mr. L.W. Frisbie (Box 36)
      - H25.01: Mr. F.D. Cheney’s Correspondence re Exhibits Includes Letters re Missing Zeppelin Model. (Box 36)
      - H25.01s: Berlin Fair - Correspondence and Press Data (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Berlin Fair - Correspondence re Securing Government Exhibit (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Brooklyn Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Danbury Fairs (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Granby Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Guilford Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Hartford (Charter Oak Fair) - Correspondence & Press Data & Pamphlets (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Harwinton Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Norfolk Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Norwich Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Riverton Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Rockville Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: South Woodstock Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Stafford Spring Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Thompsonville Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Union Agricultural Society - Enfield Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Washington Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Windsor Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Wolcott Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.01s: Woodstock Fair (Box 37)
      - H25.011: Correspondence and Recommendation re use to be made of exhibit material. (Box 37)
      - H25.099: Foreign Trade Exhibits (Box 37)
      - H25.1: Pay Roll (War Exhibits) (Box 37)
      - H25.3: Original Drafts of Fair Posters and Notices (Box 37)
      - H.29: Speaking re Food Administration (Box 37)
      - H30: Connecticut Agricultural College (Box 37)
      - H30: Connecticut Agricultural College Extension Service (Box 37)
      - H45: Farm Bureaus (Box 37)
      - H45.NL: New London County Farm Bureau (Box 37)
      - H45.21: Poster: “If you need Farm Labor, Ask For It” (Box 37)
      - H100: Increase in Production of Food (Box 38)
      - H102: Agriculture (Box 38)
      - H102: Agricultural Department of Fairfield Co. Association (Box 38)
      - H102: Agricultural Appropriation Bill (Box 38)
      - H102.05: [New England Homestead] (Box 38)
      - H102.06: Mass Meeting of Farmers, 1918 March 22 (Box 38)
      - H102.061: Connecticut Farmer’s Week (Box 38)
      - H102.07: [List of Publications, US Department of Agriculture] (Box 38)
      - H107: Weekly News Letter [USDA] (Box 38)
      - H107: [Weekly News Letter, USDA] (Box 39)
      - H109: Press Articles re Agricultural Surveys (Box 39)
      - H109: Agricultural Surveys - Litchfield County (Box 39)
      - H110: Forms For Returning Soldiers (Box 39)
      - H110.1: Increased Planting (Box 39)
      - H118: [Potash] (Box 39)
      - H119.1: [Nitrate of Soda] (Box 39)
      - H125: [Farm Machinery] (Box 39)
      - H130: Seeds (Box 39)
      - H140: Agriculture Labor (Box 39)
      - H140: Farm Labor (Herbert Knox Smith’s Folder) (Box 39)
      - H143: Women on Farms (Box 39)
      - H144: Victory Farm Helpers League (Voluntary Farm Work by Business and Professional Men) (Box 39)
      - H145: Junior food Army (Home Gardening, Canning, etc.) (Box 39)
      - H146: Boy’s Working Reserve (Box 39)
      - H146.21: Boy’s Working Reserve - Posters (Box 39)
      - H147: Connecticut Boy’s working Reserve - Boys For Farm Service Camps (Box 40)
      - H147.01: Letter of Aug. 6, 1918 to High School Principals re Help for Harvesting - List of Students (Box 40)
      - H148: Activities of Employment Service in re Farm Labor (Box 40)
      - H152: Furloughs to Enlisted Men to Enable Them to Engage In Agriculture (Box 40)
      - H210: Live stock (Box 40)
      - H210.3: Meat (Box 40)
      - H215: [Courses for Women at State Agricultural College] (Box 40)
      - H215.3: [Milk] (Box 40)
      - H216: Sheep Raising (Box 40)
      - H217: [Dogs] (Box 40)
      - H231: [Poster: “Kill the Slacker Hen”] (Box 40)
      - H270: Grain (Wheat, etc.) (Box 40)
      - H275: Flour and Feed Mills (Box 40)
      - H295: Gardens (Box 40)
      - H295.2: [Supervisors for Junior Gardeners] (Box 40)
      - H510: Markets (Box 41)
      - H510: Daily Market News Letter (US Bureau of Markets) (Box 41)
      - H630: Receipts for Cooking (Box 41)
      - H700: Preservation of Food - Canning (Box 41)
      - H800: Food Conservation (Box 41)
      - H801: Sending Food to Camps and Cantonments (Box 41)
      - H808: Hoover Pledges - Wheat Saving (Box 41)
      - H840: Sugar (Box 41)
      - H902.05: [US Food Administration, Washington DC - Official Statements] (Box 41)
      - H906.05: [US Food Administration, Little Rock] (Box 41)
      - H921.05: [Food Administration Bulletin, Boston] (Box 41)
      - H921.09: [Bulletin #19-106: Report Form For Town Committees] (Box 41)
      - H929: [Bureau of Educational Experiments, New York] (Box 41)
    - J. Industrial Survey (Box 42)
      - J: White Survey (Industrial Survey) (Box 42)
      - J: [Industrial Surveys] (Box 42)
      - J12: [Price Fixing] (Box 42)
      - J18: Manufacturer’s Association (Box 42)
      - J21: Correspondence With Manufacturers re Army Cloth and Government Contracts, 1917 May (Box 42)
      - J21: Mr. Cheney’s Correspondence re Increased Production of Olive Drab Cloth, 1918 January (Box 42)
      - J22: Factories (Box 42)
      - J23: Priority System - Priority Board (Box 42)
      - J23: Replies From State Councils Regarding National Priority Board (Box 42)
      - J24: Priorities (In Industry) (Box 42)
      - J24: Priorities (Herbert Knox Smith’s Material) (Box 42)
      - J25: Fire Prevention (Box 42)
      - J26: Conservation Association of Connecticut (Box 42)
      - J27: Fire Inspection (Box 42)
      - J27: Bissell, Rm. - Letter re Inspection of Property for Purposes of Fire Prevention, October 3 (Box 43)
      - J28: Explosives (Box 43)
      - J29: Interchange of Fire Apparatus, Mutual Fire Aid Cooperation, Hose Couplings - For Mr. Ferguson and Mr. Cheney (Box 43)
      - J31.01: Gasoline Conservation (Box 43)
      - J31.02: Automobile Riding on Sundays. Gasoline Days, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - J32: Platinum Conservation (Box 43)
      - J41: Essential & Non-Essential Industries (Box 43)
      - J45: [Waste Reclamation] (Box 43)
      - J45.1: Waste Paper. Also Saving of Paper (Box 43)
      - J50: Convict Labor (Box 43)
      - J105: Waterbury Rent Hearing (Box 44)
      - J105: Rents - Housing (Box 44)
      - J105.01: Mr. H.K. Smith’s Correspondence re Waterbury Rent Raising (Box 45)
      - J105.1: Rooming Facilities - “Rent A Room” Campaign (Box 45)
      - J200: Commercial Economy (Box 45)
      - J200: Commercial Economy - Clippings (Box 45)
      - J200.06: Conference on Commercial Economy, 1918 February 6 (Box 45)
      - J200.1: Letter to Secretaries of Chambers of Commerce re Delivery Service, 1917 July 20, August 14 (Box 45)
      - J200.2: Commercial Economy - Work by Women (Box 45)
      - J201: Wool-Yarn (Box 45)
      - J225: Containers (Box 45)
      - J226: Automobile Economy (Box 45)
      - J227: Garbage Utilization (Box 45)
      - J300: National Resources Association (Box 45)
    - K. Manpower and Labor (Box 45)
      - K: Manpower and Labor - General Material (Box 45)
      - K01: General Instructions to Manpower and Labor Committee (Box 46)
      - K01: Organization of Manpower and Labor Committee (Box 46)
      - K02: Smith, Herbert Knox - Correspondence File (Box 46)
      - K06: Minutes of Committee Meetings (Box 46)
      - K08: General Data, Memoranda, etc. (Box 46)
      - K11: Finance - Budgets, etc., of Committee on Manpower and Labor (Box 46)
      - K12: Military Census of Connecticut (Box 46)
      - K13: War Census (Box 46)
      - K14: Labor (General Material) (Box 46)
      - K15: Hours of Labor (Box 46)
      - K16: Daylight Saving (Box 46)
      - K18: Loafing - “Work or Fight” Orders (Box 46)
      - K21.2: [KWHH - Who Are They? (Poster)] (Box 47)
      - K26: Tobacco (General Material Including our Circular letters) - Reports (Box 47)
      - K26: Tobacco - Press Items (Box 47)
      - K26.1: Correspondence re Tobacco Hearings - Applications for Increased Acreage (Box 47)
      - K26.1: Tobacco Hearing Letters, 1917 December-1918 January (Box 47)
      - K26.2: Tobacco - Signed Statements of Tobacco Growers re Acreage (Box 47)
      - K25.3: Tobacco Correspondence (Box 47)
      - K26.3: Mr. Herbert Knox Smith’s Correspondence (Box 47)
      - K101: British Commission From The Ministry of Munitions (Box 47)
      - K101: British Commission From The Ministry of Munitions Correspondence (Box 47)
      - K102: Proposed Munition Personnel Bureau (Box 47)
      - K115: Shipbuilding - Circular Letter (Box 47)
      - K115: Shipbuilding - Press Data (Box 47)
      - K115: Shipbuilding - Correspondence and other Data (Box 48)
      - K185: Wages (Box 48)
      - K200: Employment of Women - Women In Industry (Box 48)
      - K205: Women’s Division of US Employment Service (Box 48)
      - K205.06: Conference Under Auspices of the Women’s Division, of the US Employment Service, 1918 December 5 (Box 48)
      - K205.2: Professional Training For Women (Box 48)
      - K230: Shortage of Labor (Box 48)
      - K230: Herber Knox Smith’s Correspondence re Labor Supply and Shortage (Box 48)
      - K231: Skilled Labor (Yellow Survey) (2 envelopes) (Box 48)
      - K231: Skilled Labor (Yellow Survey) - Circulars, Materials About Survey, etc. (Box 48)
      - K231: Skilled Labor (Yellow Survey) No.2 (Box 49)
      - K231: Address by Dorragh De Lancey, with Blanks, Forms etc. (Box 49)
      - K240: Organization of Civilian Service - US Public Service Reserve (Box 49)
      - K250: Labor Exchanges - Employment Service (Box 49)
      - K250.01: Offices of US Employment service (Box 49)
      - K250.051: State Clearance Bulletins (US Employment Service) (Box 49)
      - K250.05: [Report of the Conference Held Under the Auspices of the women’s Division, US Employment Service] (Box 49)
      - K250.07: Posters Issued by the Department of Labor (Box 49)
      - K250.08: Circular Letters of Employment Service (Box 49)
      - K250.1: [Press Releases re Tank Corps] (Box 49)
      - K250.2: Labor Mobilization - Community Labor Board (Box 50)
      - K260: Civilian Personnel Division of War Department (Box 50)
      - K270: [Press Release - Clerks for Ordinance Department] (Box 50)
      - K270.1: Bridgeport Office of the Ordinance (Box 50)
      - K275: Employment For Returning Soldiers - Labor Re-Adjustment (Box 50)
      - K275.1: Bureau For Returning Soldiers. (Box 50)
      - K275.2: Development of Public Works to Provide Employment for Returning Soldiers. (Box 50)
      - K276: Cancellation of War Contracts (Box 50)